[{"answer": "Hey! Are you ready yet", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh! Got 'em right here,  check", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah. Yeah. Yes, this place is beautiful. my friend's parents got married here", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Oh. Oh my God. How can this be happening? What are we going to do", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How's it gonna be all right?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah, we all know! We talk about it all the time", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh no, my friend doesn't know anything", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The only thing I understand i", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No. I'm saying it's now.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Okay, this is going to be harder than I thought. Umm, let's try some uh, aversion therapy", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hi. I understand you had a little talk with my friend", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Am I?! And was it your idea to postpone the wedding?", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Two pizzas?", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Wait, well, where did you get it from?!", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah, it's in the guys' apartment under the sink. Why", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What?! What do you mean you're going to that place", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Out loud", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "So how are you doing", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sure, you know what? Come on, we'll just tell them that there was like a problem with like the", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Look, If I don't get to that place!! He is going to marry that other girl!!", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh yea yea, absolutely", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't want to look", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hold on. Hold on.  my friend coming. Do...Something", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I'm not seeing my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Okay! Okay! That's it!! Parents!! Parents!! Back away!! All right, this is our wedding day!", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " It was...This disagreement over... My god. You...you look beautiful", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What we did last night was...", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Totally crazy stupid.", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I, my friend..", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Take thee my friend..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Take thee my friend..", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "As my lawfully wedded husband, in sickness and in health, until death parts us", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I my friend..", "docId": "423rowed.htm.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Take thee, my friend... my friend.  my friend", "qsentId": 38}]